有何能为您效劳的
Hi, how can I help you?
我是指
And by that, I mean,
在最不费力的范围内
what's the least I can do to help you?
我要来一份汉堡加薯条
I'll have the burger with the fries.
把她的薯条换沙拉
She'll have it with the salad.
可是我想吃薯条
But I want the fries.
你想吃是一回事  但你不该吃
Well, you want them, but you don't need them.
好吧  那就换成沙拉
Fine, the salad.
我要去洗手间
I have to pee.
-你好  你叫什么名字  -大卫
- Hi, what's your name? - David.
大卫  你该滚了
David, you should go.
你什么意思
I'm sorry?
你想她吃沙拉  她想你有头发
You want her to have salad, she wants you to have hair.
今晚这两件事都不会发生
Neither one's gonna happen tonight.
你跟薯条妹不会有好结果的
Yeah, it's not gonna work out between you and french fries.
或许能好个一周或一年
Oh, maybe it will for a week or a year.
如果儿时受虐过  则能忍比较久
Depends if she was molested as a kid.
但只要某天爆发了  她肯定跟你玩命
But one of these days, she's coming after you.
月黑风高夜  手里提着刀
Probably in the dark, probably with a knife.
手起刀落  砍掉你一两颗蛋蛋
And she's gonna cut off one or both of your balls.
到时你就不会介意她点薯条了
And you won't think a side of fries matters
因为你已是没蛋[胆]人
when you have zero balls.
给她上薯条吧
She'll have the fries.
那是必须的
Yes, she will.
你看咱俩
Look at us.
守住了一个女人的尊严
We saved another woman's dignity
以及一个男人的蛋蛋
and another man's balls.
我们就像是更合格版的菲尔医生
Yeah, we're like Dr. Phil but more qualified.
瞧我  做老板的还得去伺候客人
Well, here I am, the owner, waiting on tables.
奥巴马会去通白宫马桶吗
Does Barack Obama unclog the white house toilets?
你不觉得这有什么不妥吗
What's wrong with this picture?
我首先想到的问题就是
Well, off the top of my head,
我十分钟前就点了杯咖啡
I ordered a coffee ten minutes ago,
你现在还没给我端来
and you still haven't gotten it.
别这样  我都要忙[大麻]不过来了
Hey, man, I'm in the weeds here.
如果你有大麻  那咖啡就不要了
Well, if you got weed, cancel the coffee.
姑娘们  你们迟到啦
Uh, ladies, you're late.
天才"小"宝贝在不高兴呢
And Little Man Tate over there is in a mood.
为啥  他又开始长牙了吗
Why, is he teething again?
你们可"好"
Uh, hello.
你们十分钟前就应该到了
You were supposed to be here ten minutes ago.
在韩国  你们的头会被砍下
In Korea, your heads would be on sticks
插在三星工厂外的棒子上示众
outside the Samsung factory,
而且你们还是得继续工作呢
and you would still have to work.
你们上班要的咖啡也没有先备好
There is no coffee prepped for your shift.
"小小"女舞者  我告诉你
F.Y.I., Tiny Dancer,
没备好咖啡是上白班懒鬼的错
Prepping coffee is that lazy-ass day waiter's job,
你可别赖我们
so don't blame us.
你请了不中用的服务员不能怪我们啊
It's not our fault you hired an incompetent waitstaff.
快点  你们俩得去做咖啡
Hurry up. You two need to make coffee.
你也得去请新的上白班的员工
And you need to hire a new day waiter.
说到你要给餐厅弄新的人事物
And maybe while you're getting new things around here,
买台新的咖啡机如何
how about a brand-new coffeemaker?
买台没出现在爱德华·霍普画中的新机
One that isn't from an Edward Hopper Painting.
我是唯一去过美术馆的人吗
Am I the only one who's been to a museum?
放尊重点好吗
Uh, excuse me.
姐也是去过寝洗具大卖场艺术摆设区的人
I've been to the art section of Bed Bath & Beyond.
如果说  我已经实现了你们的愿望呢
What if I told you I already got you what you want?
高端卡布奇诺咖啡机吗
A high-end cappuccino machine?
听好了  金发野心妹
Listen, blonde ambition.
我知道你想我买新咖啡机的原因
I know you only want me to get one,
是因为方便你们小蛋糕窗口也能卖咖啡
so you can use it at your cupcake window.
你怎么能这么说
How dare you?
但如果你乐意的话那也行啊
Unless you're comfortable with that.
不  我说的是上白班的员工
No, I meant the new day waiter.
他就在厨房里
He's in the kitchen.
去训练新人吧
Go train the new guy.
我们叫你炒掉的白班员工去哪了
What happened to the guy we told you to fire?
我们很喜欢他呢
We loved him.
好  我们现在就去训练新人
Okay, we'll go train the new guy now.
但新的咖啡机
But about that coffeemaker,
要不我们跟你一人出一半
what if go halfsies with you?
我们出不了一半
We can't afford to go halfsies.
连四分之一都出不起
We can't even go quarter-sies
八分之一  与八分之一后的也出不起
or eighth-sies or whatever's after eighth-sies.
十六分之一
Sixteenth-sies.
你们都去死吧
Shoot yourselves.
他刚说训练新人  还是训练基人
Did he say train the new guy or new gay?
你好  你一定是新的白班服务员
Hi, you must be the new day waiter.
你们一定就是上晚班
Ah, you must be the late girls
要负责训练我的女孩们
who are supposed to train me.
是的  我叫路易斯
Yes, I'm Luis.
他是说路易斯还是露易丝
Did he say Luis or Louise?
我马上就好
I'll be out in a minute.
我得等我脸上的面霜[精液]干了
I have to let this cream dry on my face.
我向来也都是等它自然干的
Oh, I always wait for the cream to dry.
这样比较礼貌
It's the polite thing to do.
我叫麦克斯
I'm Max.
麦克斯真搞笑
Oh, Max is funny.
瞧她
Look at her.
用搞笑来掩盖悲伤
Oh, funny to mask the pain.
我看穿了你
I see you.
你们俩都很漂亮啊
Oh, and you're both pretty.
看这金发妞
Look at blondie.
你整过哪里了
What have you had done?
我吗
Oh, me?
没整过  谢谢夸奖啊
Nothing, but thank you.
我叫卡洛琳
I'm Caroline.
幸会幸会  但我们不会成为朋友
Well, nice to meet you, but we won't be friends.
我不会人发展情谊
I don't get attached.
我干了一辈子的服务员  大概27年了
All my life, I've been a waiter, 27 years.
我也干了27年的服务员
I've been a waiter 27 years too,
而且我才26岁呢
and I'm only 26.
我不会过问你们的私事
And I don't get personal,
所以也别问我几岁
so don't ask me how old I am.
我53岁了
I am 53.
但我的脸蛋看上去只有5岁
But my face is 5.
你看起来容光焕发
You look amazing.
我只有两年的服务员经历
I've only been waiting tables two years.
我的主要重心摆在我们的小蛋糕生意
My main focus is our cupcake business.
我们新开了一个外卖窗口...
We just opened a walk-up window--
亲  亲  我不用知道你的人生
Honey, honey, I don't need to know your life.
你也不用知道我的
You don't need to know mine.
我爸爸有在我
Did my father put a gun in his mouth
七岁生日派对上饮弹自尽吗
at my seventh birthday party?
有的  但我也不会上班说
Yes, but I don't bring that to work.
我已经爱上你了
And I'm in love with you.
别这样
Don't do that.
别爱上我
Don't fall in love with me.
你知道那些不爱女人的基佬吗
You know those gays that don't like women?
我就是其中之一
I'm one of them.
你的铃声是《欲望都市》的主题曲吗
Is that the theme song from Sex and the City?
这还用说吗
You know it is.
我是夏绿蒂那一型的
I'm a Charlotte.
我也是
So am i!
像我们这一型的不多呢
There's not a lot of us.
我是《美国恐怖故事》中所有死姑娘那一型
I'm all the dead girls from American Horror Story.
言归正传  该干正事了
Well, let's get this train on the tracks.
跟我来  夏绿蒂
Follow me, Charlotte.
新咖啡机的事我可不会就此放弃
I'm not giving up on our cappuccino machine.
我会使劲给阿憨上"活儿"到他[射]给我为止
I'm gonna work Han hard until he gives it to me.
不用说  我也听到自己语中的歧义了
Yes, I just heard how that sounded.
路易斯  桌子是分成这样的
Okay, Luis, here's how the tables work.
有上限四人桌  也有上限两人桌
We got the four-tops. We got the two-tops.
-你也在"上"面吗  -废话
- Are you a top? - Oh, please.
价值两万五的脸蛋  哪能做"受"被压枕头上
No one is pushing this $25,000 face into a pillow.
我准备好点餐了
I'm ready to order.
路易斯  你去搞定那桌吧
Luis, why don't you take that table?
这是你的训练  而且我也不想去
It's part of your training, and I don't want to.
厄尔  他是上白班的新服务员
Earl, that's the new day waiter.
他也是新的"基"务员
He's also the new gay waiter.
我爱死男同们了
Oh, I love the gays.
他们把我家那边一间老吸毒房
They turned an old crack house in my neighborhood
装修成了奶酪店
into a cheese shop.
我听说那家奶酪店卖的毒品很不错呢
I heard that cheese shop has really good crack.
今天的例汤是什么
What's the soup of the day?
你没看见板子上怎么写的吗
What does it say on the board?
你已经出师了
And you're trained.
麦克斯  阿憨拒绝了
Max, Han said no,
我们店里需要一台好咖啡机
and we need that cappuccino maker for our shop
不然我们怎么跟街角的星巴克
if we're ever gonna compete with the Starbucks around the corner
以及另一个街角 还有另外个街角的店斗呢
or the other corner or the other corner.
还有正在我屁股上大兴土木的那家
Or the one that's currently being built in my ass.
干嘛  我那也是黄金地段好吗
What? It's prime real estate.
威廉斯堡地区已经没有任何空位了
Everything else in Williamsburg is taken.
卡洛琳  你想要卡布奇诺咖啡机吗
Caroline, you need a cappuccino machine?
我能帮你弄到便宜的  我认识个人
I can get you one cheap. I know a guy.
哪天需要干净尿液样本或迷你猪
And if you need clean urine or a micro pig,
我也有认识的人
I also know that guy.
偶的天啊  他是谁
Oh, my God. Who was that?
刚才是奥列格
Oh, that's-- that's Oleg.
他是厨子
He's the cook.
他真是太正点了
He is gorgeous.
我好兴奋
I'm so excited.
我们的新机器马上就要到了
Our new machine will be here any minute.
我们的生活要飘出卡布奇诺香啦
Our lives are about to get a lot more cappuccino-y.
或者说是卡布奇诺拿铁香
Or should I say a latte more cappuccino-y?
不  这些白痴话你就不应该说
No, you should not say any of that.
至于奥列格说要给我们的"特别价"
And as for that "special price" Oleg said he'd give us?
先说好  玩3P
In all my three-ways,
我得先上  以及不许亲吻
I'm up to bat first, and I don't kiss.
白天这里面儿可真是热
During the day, it is hot in herrr.
谢谢你的天气报告  亚瑟儿小子
Thanks for the weather report, Ursher.
货到了
Here it is.
关上窗子  然后闭嘴
Shut the windows and shut up.
这开场白跟我想的一模一样啊
Well, this is starting exactly like I imagined.
快关上
Shut it!
奥列格  你去哪弄来的机器
Oleg, where did you get this?
闭嘴
Shut up!
外面是警铃吗
Are those sirens?
闭嘴
Shut up!
有使用说明书吗
Does it come with instructions?
使用说明就是"闭上嘴"
The instructions are to shut up.
我们不要偷来的赃物
We don't want it if it's stolen.
我现在还对不花钱把DVD自动租赁机的光盘
I still feel guilty about shaking down that redbox
给弄出来而愧疚  但我本人绝对不知情
for I don't know how she does it.
这不是我偷的
I did not steal it.
我是在知情的情况下  跟偷它的人买了
I knowingly bought it from a man who stole it,
然后再转手卖了获利
and I'm selling it at a profit.
这是亚美尼亚人的方式
It's the Armenian way.
你又不是亚美尼亚人
You're not Armenian.
我知道  我只是说"这是亚美尼亚人"的方式
I know, I'm just saying, it's the Armenian way.
这零售价是六百块
It retails for $600,
但我愿意免费给你们
but I'll give it to you for free
只要你们帮我做件事
if you do me a favor.
免费吗
Free?
好吧  那让麦克斯跟你去
Okay, I guess Max can do you
旁边的更衣间来一炮吧
in that closet over there.
干嘛
What?
我不能让到嘴的鸭子飞走呀
Now that I see it, I have to have it.
好吧  养药千日  用在一时
All right, I've been saving this pill for something.
去探探苏菲的口风
Talk to Sophie.
看她有没有兴趣跟我复合
See if she wants to get back together.
但别告诉她我有这想法
But don't tell her I'm interested.
-低调行事  -行
- Do it discreetly. - Deal.
奥列格  我好感动也有点惊讶啊
And, Oleg, I'm touched and a little surprised.
我不知道你还懂"低调行事"这词
I didn't know you knew the word "discreetly"
我床边有个每日一词日历
Oh, yeah. I have a word-a-day calendar near my bed,
就在我那一大罐的凤梨味润滑剂旁
next to my big pump jar of pineapple lube.
发浪肚饿都能挤一发
For when you're horny and hungry.
麦克斯  你干嘛还吃
Max, why'd you take it?
你又不用跟他来一炮
You don't have to have sex with him.
我知道  我这是在庆祝
I know, I'm celebrating.
我在网上找不到我们咖啡机的
Hey, I can't find any of the instructions on here
使用说明书啊
for our coffeemaker.
也不怪它  我压根没找
In fairness, I haven't been looking.
我被网上一个"刺青写错字"合集的
I got sidetracked by this buzzfeed list
帖子给吸引住了
of misspelled tattoos.
有个女孩刺脖子上次了"妹子烧烤[行啊]"
This girl got "You go grill" on her neck.
她一定是很喜欢在外面煮东西
She must really like to cook outside.
你罚自己罚站面壁思过吗
Did you put yourself in a time-out?
我在蹲点等苏菲
No, I'm looking for Sophie.
她不在楼上
She's not upstairs.
为了拿免费东西
Look, this is a long way to go
这代价也太大了
to get something for free.
我很乐意去百货公司里
I was happy to walk into Sears
把咖啡机藏到我裤子里偷出来呢
and stuff a cappuccino machine down my pants.
我不是为了免费拿咖啡机才这样
I'm not doing it for the free cappuccino machine.
我是为了免费咖啡机能为我们
I'm doing it for the money we'll make
赚到的钱  才这么大费周章
from the free cappuccino machine
顺便帮奥列格与苏菲复合嘛
And maybe to help Oleg and Sophie get back together.
就像莎士比亚书中的故事  我就是帕克
You know, it's a page out of Shakespeare, and I'm Puck.
《真实世界》里的帕克吗
Puck from The Real world?
我是唯一读过书的人吗
Am I the only one who's read a book?
她来了  我来负责套话吧
Oh, here she is. I'll do the talking.
这方面算是我的强项
It's kind of in my wheelhouse.
你有个房子
You have a wheelhouse,
我们为啥要住在这垃圾堆里
and we're living in this dump?
早安啊  苏菲
Morning, Sophie.
被你抓个正着
You caught me.
我现在是炮后羞愧地走回家
I'm doing the walk of shame.
你们懂意思的吧
You know what that means, right?
我昨晚跟一个陌生人"大战"了一宿
I was having sex all night with a stranger.
我也跟个男的床战一宿过
I had sex with a guy all night once.
反正他是这么说的  我十点就睡着了
At least that's what he said. I fell asleep at 10:00.
苏菲  进来吧
Sophie, come in.
我们想问你一件要紧事
We wanted to ask you something kind of important.
好
Oh, okay.
好吧  那我就说了
Well, I'll tell you.
我觉得你的小蛋糕生意不会成功
I don't think you're gonna make it in the cupcake business.
地铁站的灵媒跟你说的相反
Not what the psychic in the subway told me,
但我会铭记在心的
But duly noted.
其实是想问你个更私人的问题
Actually, it's more of a personal question.
行  我个人认为
Oh, okay. Well, I personally
你的小蛋糕生意不会成功
don't think you're gonna make it in the cupcake business.
这问题跟奥列格有关
No, the question is about Oleg.
他也同意我这么说呢
Oh, yeah, he agrees with me.
求你了  就直说吧  免得等会
God's sakes, just tell her before she tells us
她开始描述我们以后会躲在某个烂公寓
we're gonna wind up in some disgusting apartment,
躲我们鸨母的未来
hiding from our pimp.
好啦好啦  苏菲
Okay, okay, Sophie.
你有想过跟奥列格复合吗
Do you ever think about getting back together with oleg?
天啊  当然没有
Oh, God, no.
我宁愿再发生次意外跟亲戚做爱的惨事呢
I'd rather accidently have sex again with my cousin.
我可讨厌碰到这情况了
I hate when that happens.
干嘛问
Why, did--
他问我的事了吗
did he ask about me?
没有啦  我就自己好奇
Oh, no, no. I was just wondering.
他从来没提过你
He never even mentions you.
那就好
Oh, good.
因为姐已经不再留恋他了  宝贝
'Cause I moved on, baby.
惨了  惨了  我...
Oh, no. No, I--
我把我的塑身衣忘在斯塔顿岛了
I left my Spanx on that Staten Island stoop.
是好的那套呢  你懂吧
And they're the good ones, you know,
有尿洞的那种
with the pee hole in them.
我得去拿回来
I gotta go grab 'em.
好了  再见
All right. Bye-bye.
好了  我们已经把电源插上了
Okay, good. Now we've got the power on,
但是要怎么蒸牛奶
but how do we steam the milk?
也许是要按这触控板
Maybe it's on this touchpad thing.
我去你个亲娘七舅老爷
Holy mother of God!
我的"小妹妹"被蒸熟了
I just steamed my vagina.
麦克斯  卡洛琳  你们三分钟前就该上班了
Max, Caroline, your shift started three minutes ago.
谁还在乎这份烂兼职
Who cares about sidework?
我可能这辈子都生不了小孩了
I probably can't have children.
她怎么了
What is wrong with her?
她刚用蒸汽清洗了她的"地毯"
She just had her carpet steam-cleaned.
你们俩还没搞懂怎么用这台机器吗
You two still haven't figured out this machine?
走开  我是亚洲男人
Move away. I'm Asian and a man.
我对这种东西很在行
I'm good with this kind of stuff.
阿憨  算了吧  这玩意挺危险的
Well, Han, actually, it's pretty dangerous.
你最近没听说吗  人家阿憨是个"男人"
Hey, Han's a man, according to recent lore.
让他来拯救世界吧
Let him save the day.
好吧  我看看  这个按钮是蒸汽
Okay, let's see. Here's the steam one.
这个按钮是...
And here's the button for-- ow!
我的脖子
My neck!
它烫伤了我的脖子
It burned my neck!
那可是我最迷人的部位了
And that was my best feature.
还好你不够高
Luckily you're not taller.
不然你烫伤的就是阴道啦
You would've burned your vagina.
那台卡布奇诺咖啡机刚可能
That cappuccino machine might have just
给我做了个"大杯"级子宫切除术
given me a grande hysterectomy.
卡洛琳  我知道现在时机可能不好
Caroline, I know this might not be a good time.
我有听说你的鲍鱼被烤了
I heard about your recent clambake.
但我想知道苏菲怎么说
But what did Sophie say?
抱歉  奥列格  苏菲对你已不再留恋
I'm sorry, Oleg. Sophie's moved on.
她现在跟其他男人约会
She's seeing other men.
对  但不是在你的那一区
Yeah, but not in your neighborhood.
她很会"做"
She's classy.
她很尊重地跑到斯塔顿岛的一个小门廊"做"
She had the decency to do it on a stoop in Staten Island.
她居然没叫上我  自己去那个岛
She went to the island without me?
我们说好要一起环游世界的
We were going to travel the world together.
奥列格
Oleg--
奥列格  你是在哭吗
Oleg, are you crying?
不  我只是鼻屎太多堵得慌
No, I have a booger situation.
此话出自我们餐厅大厨之口
Says the man who cooks the food.
那里面是什么地方
Hey, what's this area back there?
那是我们的衣橱  怎么了
Uh, it's our closet, why?
我应该进去看看
I should check it out.
我一直在找地方
I'm always looking for places
能让我带不是苏菲的女人去做爱
to have sex with women who are not Sophie.
奥列格在这里吗
Is Oleg in here?
我闻到他的体香了
I thought I smelled him.
男人味和奶油混合在一起的香味
That delicious mix of man and butter.
奥列格在"柜里"呢
Oleg's in the closet.
亲爱的  你不说我也知道
Oh, honey, I could've told you that.
路易斯  奥列格真的是直男
Really, luis, Oleg is straight.
等我下菜单的时候
Wait till you see what happens
要一份"硬骨"肋眼牛排  你就知道了
when I place an order for a bone-in rib eye.
真的  他几乎每天露鸟都给我们看
It's true. He shows us his penis every--
底线啊  姑娘们  底线
Ah-ah-ah-ah, boundaries, girls, boundaries.
那他那只是神雕吗
So is it a nice one?
他的"雕兄"有次还帮我开门了呢
Well, it did open a door for me once.
路易斯  或许你能帮我们个忙
Hey, Luis, maybe you can help us.
你是个生活家
Since you're a lifer,
你肯定知道这咖啡机要怎么操作
you have to know how to work this thing.
不  不可能  我是为餐厅工作
No, no, no, no, no, no, I work for a diner.
又不是为你俩工作
I don't work for you.
别把我牵扯进你们的事里
Don't bring me into your drama.
我得接下电话
Oh, I have to get this.
是我妈  她在守灵
It's my mother. She's on death watch.
但我在星巴克工作时
But we used to have the same machine
用的咖啡机跟这台一样
When I worked at Starbucks.
妈咪  你还好吗[西语]
Mami, como esta su lou gehrig's?
不  我才不去星巴克打工
No, I am not working at Starbucks.
我没想要这么说呀
That's not what I was gonna say.
只是去打两小时工而已嘛
Just for two hours.
等我们学会怎么用之后就可以不干了
We can quit after we learn how to work this damn machine.
老娘从不说不干就不干
Hey, I am not a quitter.
老娘只能是被炒  这是我的强项
I get fired. That's my wheelhouse.
真不敢相信这么快工作就到手了
I can't believe we got hired so quickly.
我也不敢相信我居然得穿中号的围裙
And I can't believe I'm a medium apron.
我也不敢相信我在
And I can't believe I'm working
一家连锁咖啡店上班
for a corporate coffee place.
这或许是我人生的最低点
This might be the lowest point of my life,
我妈有次在赌场后面玩垃圾游戏
and my mom once lost me
把我弄丢  我都没这么低落
in a craps game behind a casino.
你好  我们是来受训的新员工
Hi, we're here to be trained.
我知道  真是太不幸了
I know. That's unfortunate.
我叫德文
My name's Devon.
那才叫不幸呢
Well, that's unfortunate.
咱们赶紧开始吧
Let's get this over with.
我还有很多地方得去呢
I have a lot of other places I need to be.
比如你住的老妈家地下室吗
Like your mom's basement?
你没必要在这给我甩脸色
Hey, you don't have to give me attitude.
我是没必要  但我爽这样做
I don't have to, but it's my pleasure.
抱歉  德文  她可能有点难以接受
Sorry, Devon. It's just that it's hard for her,
因为你的名字叫德文
'cause your name is Devon.
你们俩到底是什么  俩作家吗
So what are you girls? Writers?
民谣二重唱  还是俩贱人
Folk duo? Just bitches?
说对了  废柴
Nailed it, loser.
麦克斯  别咄咄逼人了
Max, pace yourself.
我们只需再忍1个小时50分钟就好
We need this job for another hour and 50 minutes.
好吧  说正事  我得在这工作多久
Okay, but for real, how long do you gotta work here
才享有医保待遇
before the health insurance kicks in?
包括牙医吗
And is there dental?
因为我里面有一颗没用的烂牙
'cause I got a dead tooth doing nothing for me.
工作30天之后才享有医保
The insurance kicks in after 30 days.
这是工会提供的  不是廉价的那种医保
But it's a PPO, not an HMO.
我们另一份工作里已经有一位基佬了
Oh, we just got an HMO at our other job.
他是夏绿蒂那型的
He's a Charlotte.
好吧  开始了
Okay, here we go.
我们做什么咖啡都要用到这台机子
Look, this is the machine we use for everything.
操作非常容易
It's incredibly easy to work
除非你是笨蛋
unless you're stupid,
如果是的话  请趁早告诉我
In which case, tell me now.
德文  我们不是你恶毒的继父
Devon, we're not your mean stepdad.
快教我们如何操作这台机子吧
Just show us how to use the machine.
听好了
Listen up.
先从热水流出来的口把过滤斗拿出来
Unlatch the portafilter from the group head.
按这里弄出一盎司的咖啡粉
Press here for an ounce of grounds.
再塞进去  压实  打开按钮
Tamp it in, pack it down, turn it on.
我没听明白  你呢
I didn't get that, did you?
老实说  我只听见流水的头
Honestly, all I heard was group head.
反正就是塞进去  压实  扭把手
So you tamp, pack, turn the knob,
等3秒  水烧开需30秒  然后把咖啡倒出来
Wait 3, blast for 30, then you pour the shot.
等牛奶热到103度后  把蒸汽棒倾斜45度角
Place the steam wand halfway in the pitcher
放进奶缸的一半左右  制作奶泡
at a 45-degree angle until the milk is 103 degrees.
你是想说做制作冰毒比制作咖啡简单多了吗
So what you're saying is it's easier to make meth?
糖浆  咖啡粉  生奶油都在这里
Syrups, powders, whipped cream is right here.
你们俩有用过这玩意吗
You ever work with one of these?
我觉得应该不难  我是华顿商学院毕业的
I think I can handle it. I went to Wharton.
-我还是哈佛毕业的呢  -我是少教所毕业的
- Well, I went to Harvard. - And I went to juvie.
而结果我们仨都穿着围裙在这里打工
And we're all here wearing an apron.
大杯双份无脂卡布奇诺
A grande double cap, non-fat.
大杯双份  无脂卡布奇诺
Grande double cap, non-fat.
喵喵  喵喵喵
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow.
超大杯三份卡布奇诺  不加鲜奶油
A venti triple cap, no whip.
Venti triple cap, no whip.
喵喵  喵喵喵
Meow, meow, shmeow, meow.
大杯双份豆奶拿铁
Grande double soy latte.
-收到了吗  麦克斯  -没有
-  Got it, Max? - Nope.
咖啡好了吗  麦克斯
Where's those drinks, Max?
正在做  快好了
Working on it, getting close.
结果全"喷"到自己身上了
And I finished all over myself.
果然是我的风格
That's so me.
拜托  麦克斯  没这么难吧
Come on, Max, it can't be that hard.
你们俩  换一换
You two, switch.
我得多拿点纸巾出去
I gotta put out more napkins.
那个女人分手互助协会来了
That Women's Breakup Support Group is here,
她们会用光咱们的纸巾
And they tap us out.
你以为她们现在就在哭吗
Think they're crying now?
等没了蛋糕棒棒糖  你再听听
Just wait till we run out of cake pops.
我要中杯卡布奇诺  三份浓缩  半低咖啡因
I'll have a tall cap, triple-shot half caf.
小渣渣  打奶头 半半
Small scrap, nipple slap, half half.
这不是我的原话
That's not what I said.
中杯卡布奇诺  三份浓缩  半低咖啡因吗
Tall cap triple-shot half caf?
姑娘  你还真行
Girl, you're good at this.
你真适合在星巴克工作
You should work at Starbucks.
我是很厉害  我觉得我会操作这台机子了
I am good. I think I'm getting the hang of this.
现在我得先
Now I just have to--
我擦咧  疼死老娘了
Holy mother of-- ouch!
这台咖啡机一定是仇视女性
This thing hates women so much,
我们应该管它叫"德州"
We should call it Texas.
或是俄亥俄州
Or Ohio.
或者老实说  美国大部分地区都这样
Or, to be honest, most of America.
我要一杯热腾腾的中杯滴滤咖啡
I'll have a tall drip, extra hot.
请问你您贵姓
Uh, what's your name?
格雷格  木字旁的格
Gregg, with thres "G"s.
好的  我就画一个鸡鸡的图案好了
Yeah, you're gonna be this picture of a penis.
你也太没礼貌了
That's rude.
现在我再送它顶帽子
Now it has a hat on it.
它在跟你说"你好"
It's saying, "Good day."
你想让我去找你们的经理谈谈吗
Do you want me to talk to your manager?
没错  再等20分钟
Yeah, in about 20 minutes,
等她学会怎么用这台咖啡机再去
after she learns this machine.
你好
Hi.
维拉要一杯超大杯无脂的滴滤咖啡
I'll take a non-fat venti drip for Vera
弗兰要一杯中杯的拿铁
And a tall latte for Fran
再来一杯加11包代糖的姜汁鲜奶拿铁
And a gingerbread latte with 11 splendas.
你们俩能给我解释一下这个吗
Can you two explain what this is?
这不是显而易见的吗
I'd say it's pretty obvious.
那是一个带着帽子的鸡鸡
That's a penis wearing a hat.
为什么
Why?
因为它秃头没安全感啊
Because it's bald and a little insecure.
好吧  你们俩被解雇了
Dudes, you're, like, fired.
拜托  德文
Come on, Devon.
再给我20分钟学习怎么用这台机子
We just need 20 more minutes to learn that machine.
-拜托了  -不行
- Please? - No.
把你们的围裙和帽子摘下
Return your aprons and caps.
还有不要想着
And do not even think
把三明治装到口袋里带走
about putting sandwiches in your pockets.
太没天理了
What?
辛苦"做"了那么久  连个面包都不给拿吗
A girl can't get a morning bun?
不行  绝对不行
No and no.
还有把你们做的这杯"屎不奇诺"带走
And take this "crappuccino" you made with you.
的确  味道不太对
Oh, yeah, that is not quite right.
我的烂牙开始疼了
And it hit my dead tooth.
你牛奶弄得怎么样
How you doing with that milk?
很好
Great.
我打出来的奶泡比用尼克·卡农的舌头还厉害
Mine's more whipped than Nick Cannon.
你们好呀  姑娘们
Hola, chicas.
你们的新咖啡机用得怎么样了
How's it going with your new machine?
就问问  完全没有关心成分
Not that I care or am invested at all.
我觉得我的要做好了
Oh, I think mine's coming.
要来了
I think mine's coming.
自己来不来[高潮]  你都不知道啊
You don't even know if you're coming or not?
果然是你的风格
That's so you.
你们有见到奥列格吗
Have you seen Oleg?
从他出[了衣]柜之后  就再也没见过他了
No, not since he came out of the closet.
你找他干嘛
Why are you looking for him?
关你什么事
How is this your business?
因为你问我  "有没有见过奥列格"
Because you said, "Have you seen Oleg?"
对哦
You got me.
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
嘴巴那么毒  内心一定有很多苦吧
So much spice, so much pain.
被你发现了
You got me.
各位好呀
Hey, everybody.
你好呀  奥列格  这位是你妹吗
Hola, Oleg, and Oleg's sister?
她是萨莎
This is Sasha.
我们昨晚认识的
We met last night
早上又重新"认识"了几次
and a few times this morning.
帮我个忙
But do me a favor.
不要告诉苏菲吗
Don't tell Sophie about this?
不  尽管告诉她
No, do tell her.
老子也看开了
I've moved on.
她留下的那个"洞"  我已经填满了
I filled that hole she left.
走吧
Come on,
在你叔叔没醒之前
let's get you back to your uncle's house
赶紧送你回去
before he wakes up.
很多基佬都会这样
Oh, it happens to a lot of gays.
一旦出柜  他们就会恐慌
They come out, they freak out,
然后又躲进去
they go back in.
但我看到了他的心
But I see him.
我会一直在这里等着  等到他看见我的心
And I'll be here until he sees me.
你好呀  妈咪
Hola, mami.
夏绿蒂注定是飞蛾扑火啊
Charlotte's headed for a fall.
我成功了  我做了一杯完美的卡布奇诺
I did it. I made a perfect cappuccino.
虽然我全身有75%被烫伤  但我成功了
75% of my body is burned, but I did it.
味道如何
So how is it?
我们一定要把这小渣渣
We are so putting the small scrap,
打奶头 半半咖啡加入餐单
nipple slap, half half on the menu.